jolyday.com 2019-06-30

# Privacy Policy | Jolyday Instagram Viewer

Thank you for visiting jolyday.com Please make sure to read this privacy policy very carefully before you use the Jolyday. If you do not agree with any of it, please do not use our Jolyday. By using or accessing the Jolyday, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

At Jolyday we value the privacy of our users and it’s important for us that you understand what happens to the information you provide to us. This document is to help you understand how we use, store, collect and disclose your data.

#### Collection of Information

You are free to browse this Jolyday without revealing any personal information making it possible to identify you. However, once you have sent us your identifiable personal information, you are no longer anonymous to us. We collect two types of information from Users/Organizers of the Jolyday: “Automatic Anonymous Information” and “Identifiable Personal Information”.

#### Automatic Anonymous Information

The Jolyday/Contest Tool make it possible to monitor certain information automatically, based on your behaviour. This information does not identify you personally. We use this information to improve the Content and functionality of the Jolyday/Contest Tool, and to better understand and satisfy our visitors. This information may include the browser you use, your IP address or other information. This information is referred to herein as the AAI.

#### Identifiable Personal Information (IPI)

IPI is individually identifiable information about you that allows us to identify or contact you. Some of the Jolyday’s functions require asking you for certain IPI, such as your instagram username, instagram password and/or other personal information.

But we do not handle your Instagram passwords directly. We use Instagram's API and OAuth 2.0 protocol to authorize Our users. Our databases are secured with passwords to guard against unauthorized access of Our systems. Only engineer staff members may access data on a need-to-know basis.

You may choose to provide IPI in order to access certain functions on the Jolyday. You can always choose not to provide certain information, but in that case it may be that you cannot use certain of the Jolyday’s functions.

#### Sharing of Information to third parties

The Jolyday will target advertising based on personal information provided by users and inferred from Jolyday usage. This may include gender, age, or geographic data. Jolyday does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. We may bundle and share the non-personal information we collect from you and other users with advertisers, third parties, trusted partners and affiliates so that they display advertising that better suits your interests. We may aggregate your PII with information about others. In that case we will make your information non-personally identifiable by removing your name and other characteristics that would identify it as you. We may use and/or share the resulting non-PII with third parties. We may provide some non-personal information to others who help us understand how you use the Jolyday.

#### Sharing and Disclosure of Information to any authority parties

We may be required by law enforcement, government administrators, and/or judicial authorities to provide personally identifiable information. We will disclose personally identifiable information upon receipt of a court order, or if required to co-operate with law enforcement, administrative or other governmental agencies. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that We in good faith believe to be unlawful.

#### Cookies

We use cookies to collect non personal information, help smooth user experience, remember you on future visits, better understand how users engage with the Jolyday so we can enhance the User experience.

The use of these cookies is optional; you can configure your browser not to accept, or to only sometimes accept, cookies.

However, for optimum use of Jolyday, we advise you to accept our cookies. Certain functions may require the use of cookies in order to function correctly.

#### Connecting With Social Media.

When sign in to your Jolyday account through instagram, you are allowing us to have access to both PII and non-PII from your social media profile. That PII may be publicly viewed and may possibly be used by other members of these Jolyday's.

#### Changing of Our Policy

This Privacy Policy is subject to change at anytime. You should periodically check back and review this Privacy Policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and with whom we share it.

#### Commenting or posting on the Jolyday

When you post information (a tag, a link, a comment…) on the Jolyday, the information may be consulted or used by any User; we therefore invite you to take care when posting, as this can lead to you receiving unsolicited information from Users.

#### Links

On the Jolyday you will find various links directing you to Third Party Jolyday or to Third Party Content. Jolyday shall not be liable for the links posted by Users or the privacy policies of such third parties. This Privacy Policy, do not govern to Third Party Jolyday or to Third Party Content which the User accesses from the Jolyday.

#### Contact

For any questions concerning this Privacy Policy, other policies for the Jolyday or how to use the Jolyday, please contact us. [info@jolyday.com](mailto:info@jolyday.com)
